<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>English-1010s on HomeWork ʕ•ᴥ•ʔ</title>
    <link>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-1010/</link>
    <description>Recent content in English-1010s on HomeWork ʕ•ᴥ•ʔ</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 12:47:22 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-1010/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Literature Review</title>
      <link>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-1010/literature-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 12:47:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-1010/literature-review/</guid>
      <description>Costs and Benefits Associated with College
The world around us puts in great value and pride in universities and college education. This influences many students to attend and graduate college. At the end of the day, students may not value the education they receive in college, but they will value their diploma. A sheet of paper that would normally have little or no value is given tremendous value. Only because of the perception and value society offers it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editorial</title>
      <link>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-1010/editorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 12:47:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-1010/editorial/</guid>
      <description>Texas Social Media Censorship Law
The Supreme Court blocked a Texas law from being passed. This law would ban large social media companies from blocking posts based on their views. This would include posts such as &amp;ldquo;Russia’s propaganda claiming that its invasion of Ukraine is justified, ISIS propaganda claiming that extremism is warranted, neo-Nazi or K.K.K.&amp;rdquo; (Liptak) Lucio Vasquez from Houston Public Media states that the bill was introduced after several conservatives, including Donald Trump, were banned from these platforms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Documentary Review</title>
      <link>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-1010/documentary-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 12:47:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-1010/documentary-review/</guid>
      <description>Eating Our Way to Extinction Analysis
The documentary Eating Our Way to Extinction was released on Earth day in 2021. It claims that society needs to move towards a plant-based diet. Otherwise, society risks climate change, environmental damage, species extinction, hunger, poverty, disease, and antibiotic resistance. Due to the increasing demand for meat, the meat industry expands every year which leads to forests getting destroyed in order to create more room for animal agriculture.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
