<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on HomeWork ʕ•ᴥ•ʔ</title>
    <link>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on HomeWork ʕ•ᴥ•ʔ</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 21:37:28 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Journals 1</title>
      <link>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/financial-lit/journals-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 21:37:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/financial-lit/journals-1/</guid>
      <description>Journal 1: I realized how much your mindset matters. You can be more than capable and hold yourself back if you don’t have a growth mindset. I’ve seen this myself. I often doubt my abilities hold certain projects back because they are risky and I don’t believe in myself enough to pull them off. I’ve learned that with this mindset, everything I do won’t be enough. I need to be able to believe in myself and push myself to see that even through failure I can find success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Survey of the Conversation</title>
      <link>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-2015/survey-of-the-conversation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 18:31:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-2015/survey-of-the-conversation/</guid>
      <description>Recent developments in artificial intelligence have taken the world by storm. Large language models, stable diffusion generative image technologies, and automatic speech recognition neural networks have led to a rise in AI tools and technologies. Many predict that the next generation of software and search engines will utilize these AI tools to further assist users.
“The recent development of machine learning capabilities has resulted in an increased number of AI generated works and an understanding that humans are no longer the only source of creativity or innovation” (Hristov, 2016).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI Copyright Notes</title>
      <link>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-2015/ai-copyright-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 16:20:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-2015/ai-copyright-notes/</guid>
      <description>Artificial intellegience and the copyright dilemma. Article
Photography and AI copyright correlation The 1884 Supreme Court case of Burrow-Giles Lithographic Co. v. Sarony first extended copyright protection to photography. The camera used to capture the image of writer Oscar Wilde by photographer Napoleon Sarony was considered by the court as a tool which aided the “author” in creating “an original work of art.”
Since the image created by a digital camera or smart phone is actually computer-generated, it may very well be compared to the creation of an art work using an AI program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Planning Write</title>
      <link>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/financial-lit/financial-planning-write/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 21:37:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/financial-lit/financial-planning-write/</guid>
      <description>Planning out my work can have remarkable effects on productivity, time management, and overall success in achieving goals. Planning out work is a crucial step in organizing and prioritizing tasks. By taking the time to map out my responsibilities and deadlines, I am able to visualize the big picture and make a strategy to tackle each task effectively. This can lead to increased productivity, as I am able to focus on one task at a time and eliminate distractions and procrastination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research Paper 1</title>
      <link>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-2015/research-paper-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 18:10:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-2015/research-paper-1/</guid>
      <description>Becoming Effective Academic Writers
Building a house requires a great deal of discipline, dedication, and work. It requires a solid foundation, careful planning and design, and the use of appropriate materials to create a finished product that is strong, functional, and aesthetically pleasing. Academic writing is very similar to building houses; it demands commitment and an attention to detail. Like many I found great difficulty in writing academic pieces. My essays lacked a cohesive structure, flow, and my arguments were often weak and not well-supported by evidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary Classification Evaluation Essay</title>
      <link>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-2015/summary-classification-evaluation-essay/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 21:41:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-2015/summary-classification-evaluation-essay/</guid>
      <description>Summary, Classification, &amp;amp; Evaluation Essay
“Is Academic Writing Becoming More Informal?” by Ken Hyland and Feng Jiang examines the slow increase in the use of informal features in academic writing. The authors suggest that this is due to changing rhetorical practices and that informality can help strengthen arguments. The article concludes that the use of informal features is positive, as it makes the writing more engaging and accessible to a wider audience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Final Essay</title>
      <link>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/communications-2110/final-essay/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 12:27:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/communications-2110/final-essay/</guid>
      <description>Final Essay
The skills and knowledge gained from Communications 2110 can be extremely useful and applicable in daily life, as effective communication is a crucial aspect of building and maintaining personal and professional relationships. The course&amp;rsquo;s emphasis on understanding the complexities of communication, including the influence of language, culture, and personal experiences, can help individuals to better navigate and understand the perspectives of others. The HURIER listening model and Tuckman&amp;rsquo;s model of group development provide practical frameworks for improving listening and teamwork skills, respectively, which can be applied in a variety of settings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yes, But is New Media Good for You?</title>
      <link>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/communications-2110/yes-but-is-new-media-good-for-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 12:27:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/communications-2110/yes-but-is-new-media-good-for-you/</guid>
      <description>Yes, But is New Media Good for You?
New media amplifies all the greatest and most terrible things that society is capable of. Technology is always this source of danger, of risk. All of the biggest things that threaten our world at a small and large scale are all connected to misuse of technology. But at the same time, it&amp;rsquo;s that very technology that will empower us and save us. Just in the past 15 years, technology has been abused and misused in a way that has affects everyone and their daily lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Literature Review</title>
      <link>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-1010/literature-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 12:47:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-1010/literature-review/</guid>
      <description>Costs and Benefits Associated with College
The world around us puts in great value and pride in universities and college education. This influences many students to attend and graduate college. At the end of the day, students may not value the education they receive in college, but they will value their diploma. A sheet of paper that would normally have little or no value is given tremendous value. Only because of the perception and value society offers it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Listening in the Theater of the Mind</title>
      <link>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/communications-2110/listening-in-the-theater-of-the-mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 12:27:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/communications-2110/listening-in-the-theater-of-the-mind/</guid>
      <description>Listening in the Theater of the Mind
Listening is the key to evolution and progression. We and society both greatly benefit from the way we process and gather information. After listening to the &amp;ldquo;Three Skeleton Key,&amp;rdquo; I discovered the significance of time in the delivery of a message. The effectiveness in which a message is received is significantly influenced by time.
A common listening problem is &amp;ldquo;failure to focus on the message.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editorial</title>
      <link>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-1010/editorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 12:47:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-1010/editorial/</guid>
      <description>Texas Social Media Censorship Law
The Supreme Court blocked a Texas law from being passed. This law would ban large social media companies from blocking posts based on their views. This would include posts such as &amp;ldquo;Russia’s propaganda claiming that its invasion of Ukraine is justified, ISIS propaganda claiming that extremism is warranted, neo-Nazi or K.K.K.&amp;rdquo; (Liptak) Lucio Vasquez from Houston Public Media states that the bill was introduced after several conservatives, including Donald Trump, were banned from these platforms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unplugged</title>
      <link>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/communications-2110/unplugged/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 12:27:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/communications-2110/unplugged/</guid>
      <description>Unplugged
I believe that technology should be used to assist daily life, never to replace it. My relationship with technology is somewhat complex. I utilize it creatively to make video games, animations, and videos. But I realize that even using it in these beneficial ways, it still needs balance. I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t want to spend the rest of my life in front of a computer. I try to balance the time I spend in technology with other meaningful beneficial ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Isnt Sky Blue</title>
      <link>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/communications-2110/why-isnt-sky-blue/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 12:27:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/communications-2110/why-isnt-sky-blue/</guid>
      <description>Why isn&amp;rsquo;t the Sky Blue?
Our perception of reality is often communicated through words. Verbal communication is limited by the available words and vocabulary. We categorize our perceptions into words. Emotions, feelings, taste, smells, and colors are very difficult to describe. But once we assign these perceptions a word, it becomes very easy for everyone to understand. Without words assigned to these perceptions, our communication will be rendered ineffective. The sky is only blue because we all agreed it is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Documentary Review</title>
      <link>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-1010/documentary-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 12:47:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-1010/documentary-review/</guid>
      <description>Eating Our Way to Extinction Analysis
The documentary Eating Our Way to Extinction was released on Earth day in 2021. It claims that society needs to move towards a plant-based diet. Otherwise, society risks climate change, environmental damage, species extinction, hunger, poverty, disease, and antibiotic resistance. Due to the increasing demand for meat, the meat industry expands every year which leads to forests getting destroyed in order to create more room for animal agriculture.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
