<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on HomeWork ʕ•ᴥ•ʔ</title>
    <link>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on HomeWork ʕ•ᴥ•ʔ</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 21:37:28 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Journals 1</title>
      <link>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/financial-lit/journals-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 21:37:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/financial-lit/journals-1/</guid>
      <description>Journal 1: I realized how much your mindset matters. You can be more than capable and hold yourself back if you don’t have a growth mindset. I’ve seen this myself. I often doubt my abilities hold certain projects back because they are risky and I don’t believe in myself enough to pull them off. I’ve learned that with this mindset, everything I do won’t be enough. I need to be able to believe in myself and push myself to see that even through failure I can find success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Survey of the Conversation</title>
      <link>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-2015/survey-of-the-conversation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 18:31:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-2015/survey-of-the-conversation/</guid>
      <description>Recent developments in artificial intelligence have taken the world by storm. Large language models, stable diffusion generative image technologies, and automatic speech recognition neural networks have led to a rise in AI tools and technologies. Many predict that the next generation of software and search engines will utilize these AI tools to further assist users.
“The recent development of machine learning capabilities has resulted in an increased number of AI generated works and an understanding that humans are no longer the only source of creativity or innovation” (Hristov, 2016).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resource Summaries</title>
      <link>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-2015/resource-summaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 18:10:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-2015/resource-summaries/</guid>
      <description>Week 6: In the article,”Brief but Extremely Important Introductory Chapter that You Should Definitely Read” by Jay Jordan is all about rhetoric. “Rhetoric is the study and use of symbolic resources (especially language) that help humans cooperate with one another.” Rhetoric is also extremely helpful in writing, especially when the writer is writing to argue. In this course, argument entails assessing topics, adopting views on them, supporting those positions with arguments and supporting data, and being upfront about your ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI Copyright Notes</title>
      <link>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-2015/ai-copyright-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 16:20:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-2015/ai-copyright-notes/</guid>
      <description>Artificial intellegience and the copyright dilemma. Article
Photography and AI copyright correlation The 1884 Supreme Court case of Burrow-Giles Lithographic Co. v. Sarony first extended copyright protection to photography. The camera used to capture the image of writer Oscar Wilde by photographer Napoleon Sarony was considered by the court as a tool which aided the “author” in creating “an original work of art.”
Since the image created by a digital camera or smart phone is actually computer-generated, it may very well be compared to the creation of an art work using an AI program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Planning Write</title>
      <link>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/financial-lit/financial-planning-write/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 21:37:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/financial-lit/financial-planning-write/</guid>
      <description>Planning out my work can have remarkable effects on productivity, time management, and overall success in achieving goals. Planning out work is a crucial step in organizing and prioritizing tasks. By taking the time to map out my responsibilities and deadlines, I am able to visualize the big picture and make a strategy to tackle each task effectively. This can lead to increased productivity, as I am able to focus on one task at a time and eliminate distractions and procrastination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary Classification Evaluation Essay</title>
      <link>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-2015/summary-classification-evaluation-essay/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 21:41:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homework-plug-world.netlify.app/english-2015/summary-classification-evaluation-essay/</guid>
      <description>Summary, Classification, &amp;amp; Evaluation Essay
“Is Academic Writing Becoming More Informal?” by Ken Hyland and Feng Jiang examines the slow increase in the use of informal features in academic writing. The authors suggest that this is due to changing rhetorical practices and that informality can help strengthen arguments. The article concludes that the use of informal features is positive, as it makes the writing more engaging and accessible to a wider audience.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
